(Howard:)- Leonard?
- Yeah, buddy?
(Sheldon:)I still don't like this cushion.
(Leonard:)Okay, first of all...
(Leonard:)- ...Penny, thank you for coming.
- Oh, thanks for the shoes.
(Leonard:)Penny is an amazing shot. I think
we have a chance to win this week.
- What's the plan?
- Okay. Now, we all run out...
(Leonard:)...Sheldon and I will cut to the left
behind these trees.
(Leonard:)Raj, Howard and Leslie
flank to the right behind the rocks.
(Leonard:)We'll all have a great view as Penny
runs out and kills everyone in sight.
All right, just one thing before we start.
(Leonard:)What is it, Sheldon?
Oh!
(Penny:)What the hell?
(Sheldon:)That was for my cushion.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, Penny was our only hope.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, Leonard.
But revenge is a dish best served cold.
(Penny:)Screw that.
(Sheldon:)She can't shoot me. She's dead.
(Leonard:)He's right. You can't.
(Sheldon:)Well, if we're going to descend
into anarchy...
(Howard:)Okay. See you.
(Leonard:)Where are you going?
(Leslie:)Surrender, then Denny's.